question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song &quot;Do the Bartman&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Muse is a British (English) rock band", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Korean girl group, TWICE, consists of 9 members", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
